（忆往昔）
除去血印
Getting rid of the mark,
释放了一股能摧毁一切的力量
unleashed a force on this world.
到这世上
that could destroy it.
这肯定是黑暗干的 是吧
This is the darkness, right? It's got to be.
她一来 大家就变疯狂僵尸了吗
She shows up and everybody goes "28 days later"?
像一群疯狗一样
They were like rabid dogs.
他们不肯停下
They didn't stop.
或许是烟的关系 所有暴露在外的人
Maybe it was the smoke, and anybody who was outside,
就受到了影响
they were exposed.
他们不是人类了
That wasn't human.
有何不可 我刚杀了死亡
Why not? I killed death.
我现在什么都能接受了
I'm pretty much open for anything.
- 他们把血滴在你身上了吗 - 是的
- Did they bleed on you? - They did.
可能是会传染的
It might be transmittable.
我去
I'll go.
你救我的女儿
You save my baby girl.
她的名字是阿玛拉
Her name is Amara.
我们可以等着他们死掉
Look, we can just wait for them to die.
我们困在医院里可救不了小卡
We can't save Cass if we're stuck in some hospital.
我控制不住
I can't help myself.
他还活着
He's still alive.
兄弟们 别让我做出更可怕的事
Brothers… save me from doing worse.
好了 拿上装备
All right, let's gear up.
救人意味着要救所有人
Saving people means all of the people.
你有什么想法
What are you thinking?
带珍娜和孩子去个安全的地方
Get Jenna and the baby somewhere safe.
一枪不发地做到吗
Without a shot.
- 你能行吗 - 嗯
- Hey, you good? - Yeah.
我要送珍娜去她祖母家
I'm gonna run Jenna up to her grandmother's.
你呢 你没事吧
How about you? You okay?
不管怎样我都会找到解药的
Like it or not, I'm gonna find a cure.
我知道你会的
Yeah, I know you are.
（如今）
（内布拉斯加 苏佩里尔）
恨
H-a-t-e.
长兄该隐用这只左手
It was with this left hand that old brother Cain.
杀死了他的弟弟
struck the blow that laid his brother low.
爱
L-o-v-e.
看到这手指了吗 都弯了
You see these fingers? They're arched.
这手指的血管穿透了人的灵魂
These fingers has veins that run straight to the soul of man.
右手 朋友们 是爱之手
The right hand, friends… the hand of love.
看吧 我将给你们展现生命的故事
Now watch, and I'll show you the story of life.
这些手指 各位 总是有摩擦
These fingers, dear hearts, is always a-warrin' and a-tuggin',
打个不停
one against the other.
看好了
Now watch 'em.
左手老哥
Old brother left hand…
左手讨厌争斗
left hand hates a-fightin'.
你能说话吗
Can you talk?
看来已经没有感情了
And it looks like love's a goner.
还是已经救不回来了
Or are you too far gone?
什么
What?
没错 爱赢了
Yes, siree. It's love that won.
左手老哥的仇恨被击败了
And old left-hand hate is down for the count.
答得好
Good answer.
[邪恶力量 第11季第2集]
（爱荷华州 锡达拉皮兹市）
这一片不错啊
Well, nice neighborhood.
嗯 我差不多是在这儿长大的
Yeah. I pretty much grew up here.
在街角那边学会的骑自行车
Learned to ride my bike down the road.
初吻是在那边那栋蓝色的房子
Had my first kiss at that blue house over there.
在那边破的处
Lost my virginity up there.
蓝房那个肯定很不高兴吧
I'll bet blue house was pissed.
她是很生气
She was.
帮下忙
Do you mind?
嗯
Yeah.
小美人
Hey, beautiful.
好了
Anyway…
所以我才叫你带我们来这儿
That's why I asked you to bring us here.
发生了那么多事 这里感觉很安全
After everything that happened, it just feels safe.
好啊 有安全感很好
Well, good, safe is good.
你真会带她
You're so great with her.
没办法 女人都喜欢我
Well, what can I say, chicks dig me.
那个 我该…
Well, look, I should…
嗯 好
Right. Sure.
你们俩不会有事的
You're gonna be okay, both of you.
我知道
I know.
你和萨姆呢
What about you and Sam?
你们不会有事吧
Are you gonna be okay?
我俩对没事的标准很低
Well, for us, the bar's pretty low.
再见了
See you.
迪恩
Dean.
谢谢你
Thank you…
谢谢你做的一切
For everything.
- 珍娜 - 奶奶
- Jenna. - Hi, grandma.
你打电话来后 新闻里做了大幅报道
After you called, they did a big report on the news.
那个我讨厌的龅牙天气预报员
That weatherman I don't like with the big teeth,
他说苏佩里尔遭遇了奇怪风暴的袭击
he said some kind of freak storm hit Superior.
是啊 真是疯狂
Yeah. It was…Crazy.
你别担心 风暴要是过来了
Well, don't you worry. If that thing rolls our way.
我这儿有发电机 还有足够的罐装豆子
I've got a generator and enough canned green beans.
能坚持到审判日呢
to last till judgment day.
那太好了
Good to know.
这就是阿玛拉了吧
And this must be Amara.
真是个小天使
What a little angel.
是啊 她是个奇迹
Yeah. She's a miracle.
她父母呢
And her folks?
说来话长
It's a long story.
那等你睡醒了再说吧
Well, then it can wait till after your nap.
什么
My what?
你多久没合眼了
When's the last time you slept?
因为 我这话可是完全出于好意
Because… and I mean this is the nicest possible way…
你样子真是糟糕透顶
You look like poop on parade.
我把客卧收拾好了
Now, I made up the guest bedroom,
还把你爸以前的婴儿床搬出来了
and I got your father's old crib out for the baby,
我抱她去睡觉
so I will put her down…
没错哦
Yes, I will…
你上楼去休息一会儿 好吗
While you go upstairs and have a rest, all right?
老实说 能睡一觉真是太棒了
Honestly, a nap sounds awesome right now.
那你赶紧上楼去吧 小丫头
Well, then, you just go right upstairs, missy.
谢谢
Thank you.
谁是个小天使啊
Who's the little angel, hmm?
你也得睡觉了
You have to go to sleep.
谁是个漂亮的宝宝啊
Oh, who's a beautiful baby?
你漂亮 你最漂亮了
You are a beautiful, beautiful baby.
好了 好了
There we go. Yeah.
睡觉吧 小宝贝
Night-night, doodlebug.
（婴儿物品）
你叫什么
What's your name?
去死吧
Bite me.
好吧 去死吧
Okay, "Bite me, "
你受感染多久了
how long have you been infected?
我还想问你呢
Could ask you the same thing.
我们能闻出自己人的味儿
We smell our own.
回答我
Answer the question.
为什么
Why?
你想知道自己还剩多少时间吗
'cause you want to know how much time you got left?
我想知道一切
I want to know everything.
我有什么好处
What's in it for me?
如果我能找到解药
Well, if I can find a cure…
如果
"If."
我要点切实的东西
I want something real…
我能看得见摸得着的
…something I can hold in my hands.
比如呢
Like what?
你的布丁
Your pudding.
我昨晚被感染的
I was infected last night.
你呢
You?
今早
This morning.
等等 那为什么
Wait a second. Then why…
我比你更严重吗 我不知道
…am I further along? Don't know.
这东西 又不是数学那么精准
This thing, it ain't math.
我看见有些人转化得很快 有些人很慢
I seen some people change fast, some change slow.
但最终
But in the end…
我们的结果都一样
We all end up the same.
变成疯子
We go psycho.
然后死掉
And then we go boom.
那不…
Well, that's not…
我会解决的
I'm gonna fix this.
你撒谎
Liar!
你和我
You and me,
我们死定了
we're dead.
我们只是在慢慢死掉而已
We're just taking our sweet time about it.
如果你聪明 就一枪崩了我
So if you were smart, you'd put a bullet in me…
然后把自己也解脱了
…and then eat one yourself.
接啊 小卡
Come on, Cass.
迪恩
"Dean."
温彻斯特吗
As in Winchester?
可能是
Probably.
你来吧
Do the honors.
早啊 帅哥
Morning, handsome!
埃弗拉姆
Efram.
约拿
Jonah.
怎么…怎么回事
What's… what's happening?
我们有问题问你 卡西迪奥
We have questions for you, Castiel.
我为什么
Why am I…
我求助来着
I asked for help.
我还求一副没有牛皮癣的皮囊呢
And I asked for a vessel that didn't have psoriasis.
倒霉事年年有
Crap happens.
不
No.
不什么
No what?
不
No.
你们不明白 我被诅咒了
You don't understand. I'm cursed.
你们快跑吧
You should run.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
好像是浣熊
Sounded like raccoon…
那可不是浣熊的声音
That was not a raccoon.
（喂）
（我）
（喂我）
圣母啊 珍娜 别过去
Mary, mother… no, Jenna, don't!
珍娜 别 那女孩身体里有魔鬼
Jenna, no! The devil's in that girl!
什么
What?
我要打给怀亚特神父
I'm calling father Wyatt.
奶奶 别
Grandma, no.
那我们还能打给谁
Well, who are we gonna call?
捉鬼队
Ghostbusters.
珍娜
Jenna.
慢点说
Slow down.
怎么回事
What's wrong?
听起来像《驱魔人》里的桥段
I mean, it sounds like something out of "The exorcist."
我也这么说
That's what I said.
你觉得是恶魔吗
So you thinking demon?
或者孩子被什么感染了
Or kid got infected by something.
谁知道之前那股龙卷屁里有什么玩意
You know, who knows what was in that giant, crazy fart?
好生动 多谢了
Vivid. Thanks.
我知道你现在是一个人
Look, man, I know you're flying solo.
不 我没事 迪恩
No, I'm… I'm fine, Dean.
别担心我
Look, don't… don't worry about me.
帮助珍娜去吧
Just… just help Jenna.
你如果需要什么
And if you need anything,
就打给我
then call me.
好
Will do.
你怎么样了 僵尸之地怎么样了
How you doing? How's "Zombieland"?
挺好的
It's good.
很好
It's great.
梅塔特隆在哪
Where's Metatron?
我不知道
I don't know.
梅塔特隆在哪 卡西迪奥
Where's Metatron, Castiel?
饶了我吧 兄弟
Mercy, brother, please!
兄弟
Brother?
你算什么
What are you?
什么
W-what?
我是上帝的天使
I'm an angel of the lord.
是吗
That so?
因为 就我看来
'cause, near as I can tell,
你每次在天堂和温家兄弟间做选择时
when you have to choose between heaven and the Winchesters…
你都会选他们
you choose them.
每次都如此
Every time.
所以 你才不是我兄弟
So, see, you're not my brother.
如果要我说了算 我会拿这把利刃
And if I had it my way, I'd take this blade,
插进你的心脏
stick it in your heart…
就当这一天很完美了
…and call that a damn good day.
那动手吧
Then do it.
好玩的才刚开始
The fun's just getting started.
不
No.
（传染病）
∮ 死亡啊 ∮
∮ O death. ∮
∮ 你不再给我一年时间吗 ∮
∮ Won't you spare me over another year? ∮
∮ 我看不到的这是什么 ∮
∮ Oh, what is this that I can't see. ∮
∮ 冰冷的手擒住了我 ∮
∮ With ice-cold hands taking hold of me? ∮
∮ 当上帝已去 魔鬼掌权 ∮
∮ When God is gone and the devil takes hold. ∮
∮ 谁将宽恕你的灵魂 ∮
∮ Who'll have mercy on your soul? ∮
萨姆
Hey, Sam.
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
你是谁
Who are you?
你是想问 「什么」吧
Think you mean "What?"
给你个提示
Here's a hint.
你和你哥哥 最近让我们生意兴隆
You and your brother been real good for business lately.
你是死神
You're a reaper.
答对了
The circle gets the square.
你叫什么
What's your name?
你是在跟我调情吗 小子
Mm, you flirtin' with me, kid?
别介意 但你不是我喜欢的型
'cause, no offense, but you ain't my type.
我也不想亲近
And I'm not looking to get friendly.
帮忙宰了我老板的人
with the man who helped gut my boss.
死骑的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about Death.
我也很遗憾
So am I.
但还有人在死
But people are still dying,
所以我得做我的工作 收集灵魂
so…work to do, souls to collect…
传递消息
Messages to deliver.
什么样的消息
What kind of messages?
结束了
It's over.
什么结束了
What's over?
你和迪恩
You and Dean…
反反复复地死去活来
dying and coming back again and again.
以前的死骑觉得这挺好玩
The old Death thought it was funny.
但现在 这世界只有一条铁律
But now there's one hard, fast rule in this universe.
生者皆有一死
What lives…dies.
所以你和你哥哥下次再死了
So the next time you or your brother bite it,
你们是别想上天堂了
well, you're not going to heaven…
也别想下地狱
or hell.
我们中的一个 真希望是我
One of us… and, lord, I hope it's me…
会犯个错误
we're gonna make a mistake.
把你们丢进虚无
and toss you out into the empty.
那是回不来的
And nothing comes back from that.
我知道你要死了
I know you're dying.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
你不洁 《圣经》意义上的不洁
You're unclean in the Biblical sense.
我们回见了 萨姆
So I'll be seeing you again, Sam…
不久就能再见
Seeing you real soon.
对了 我叫比莉
Name's Billie, by the way.
再问一遍 梅塔特隆在哪
Again, Metatron… where is he?
我不知道
I don't know.
但你把他劫出了天堂
But you broke him out of heaven.
- 是啊 - 还抢了他的能量
- Yes. - And took his grace.
是的
Yes.
你还指望我们相信
And you expect us to believe he, what,
他没了法力和翅膀 还能从你手下逃脱吗
just gave you the slip… no powers, no wings?
梅塔特隆耍了我
Metatron tricked me.
那么你就是蠢了
So you're just stupid.
或者是在撒谎
Or he's lying.
是啊
Or that.
只有一个办法能一探究竟
One way to find out.
我们先割下哪里
What should we cut off first?
这里
Eeny?
Meeny?
这里
Miny?
还是这里
Or moe?
够了
That's enough.
汉娜
Hannah.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
审问他
Getting answers.
不
No.
我们不这么做事
This isn't how we do things.
出去
Get out.
Out!
谢谢你
Thank you.
先别谢我
Don't thank me yet.
出事了 卡西迪奥 可怕的事
Something's happened, Castiel… something horrible.
（礼拜堂）
那个
So…
我知道我很久没祈祷了 但是…
I know it's been a long time, but…
迪恩和我 我们经历了很多坏事
Dean and I, we've… we've been through a lot of bad.
但这次不一样
But this is different.
这次是我的错 我不知道该怎么补救
This is my fault, and I don't know how to fix it.
如果我必须死
And if I have to die,
这我早已接受 但是
I've made my peace with that, but…
求你
Please.
迪恩命不该如此
Dean deserves better.
迪恩该活下去
Dean deserves a life.
现在有人 好人
There are people out there, good people,
因我而蒙受折磨
who are going to suffer because of me,
我不是在求你替我收拾烂摊子
and I am not asking you to clean up my mess.
我都不知道你是不是还在
Hell, I don't even know if you're out there, but…
但如果你在
if you are…
如果你能听到我 我…
and if you can hear me, I, um…
我们需要帮助 上帝
we need your help, God.
我们需要知道希望尚存
We need to know there's hope.
我们需要个启示
We need a sign.
那什么意思
What does that mean?!
孩子呢
Where's the kid?
我们又有新问题了
We got another problem.
猜到了
Figures.
我想阻止她的
I tried to stop her,
但我奶奶是虔诚的天主教徒
but my grandma's real Catholic,
发生那事后 她叫来了神父
and after the crazy, she called her priest,
神父派来了一位驱魔人
who sent over an exorcist.
不是吧
Really?
是啊
Yeah.
你好啊 孩子
Hello, my son.
克劳力
Crowley.
是克劳力神父
Father Crowley.
你们认识吗
Do you know each other?
是的
Oh, yes.
迪恩当年是个很可爱的祭台助手呢
Dean was a rather scrumptious young altar boy.
我们能出去谈谈吗 神父
Can I talk to you outside…father?
当然
Of course.
我先喝个茶的
After I finish my tea.
不
No.
这样更安全
This is safer.
梅塔特隆的事我没撒谎
I wasn't lying about Metatron.
我知道
I know.
但现在 我更担心你
But right now, I'm more worried about you.
你能治好我吗
Can you heal me?
不能
I can't.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这法术十分强大
This… it's…powerful magic.
不是吧 克劳力神父 你不是吧
Really? Father Crowley? Really?
抱歉 上了年纪的可怜虫过气摇滚明星
I'm sorry, aging, pathetic, has-been rock star.
我是触犯到你敏感的情绪了吗
Did I offend your delicate sensibilities?
你跑哪去了
Where have you been?
你弟弟和那个白痴天使
Your brother and that idiot angel,
你知道他们最近在捣鼓什么吗
do you know what they've been doing?
我听说了
I've heard.
一切吗
Everything?
听了不少了
Enough.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
跟你一样 查案子
Same as you… I'm working the case.
我感到咒语陷得越来越深
I feel the spell just cutting deeper and deeper,
我想抵抗
and I'm trying to fight it.
我尽力抵抗的
I'm trying, but…
这跟内布拉斯加州
Does it have anything to do.
苏佩里尔的骚动有关吗
with the disturbance in Superior, Nebraska?
你也知道吗
You know about that?
天堂的警报大作 卡西迪奥
Alarms have been sounding in heaven, Castiel…
这警报从来没响过
Alarms that haven't gone off in…ever.
我们都不知道那是什么意思
We don't even know what they mean.
那是为黑暗准备的警报
Those alarms are for the Darkness.
黑暗只是个传说
The Darkness is a story.
不 不是的 是真的
No, it's not. It's real.
黑暗
The Darkness…
自从创世之处就被锁起来了
It's been locked away since the dawn of creation.
现在它被释放了
And now it's free.
不管是出什么问题了 迪恩都会解决的
Whatever's wrong, Dean will fix it.
上帝保佑
God help us.
别指望他了
I wouldn't count on that.
没事了
Yeah, it's okay.
它在哪
Where is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
那谁知道 温家兄弟吗
Then who would? The Winchesters?
卡西迪奥 如果这是真的 那我们都完了
Castiel, if this is true, it's the end for all of us.
萨姆和迪恩 他们在哪
Sam and Dean… where are they?
我不知道
I don't know.
那就好好想想
Then think harder!
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我在天主教会有眼线
I have sources in the Catholic church…
欠我人情的修女
Nuns that owe me a favor,
有些癖好的神父
priests with a taste for…
好了 嗯 我想象得出
Okay, all right, yeah, I can imagine.
你真心想不到
You really can't.
总之 他们听说有恶魔附体 就找到我
Anyhow, they hear of a demonic possession, they call me.
如果是我的人 我就叫他们别管
If it's one of mine, I tell them to ignore it.
如果是乱来的恶魔
If it's a, uh, demon gone rogue,
那克劳力神父就要出场了
well, that's when father Crowley comes out to play.
那么你觉得里面是个恶魔
So you think there's a demon in there.
完全不是
Not even a little bit.
我救了你
I saved you.
不 我不这么认为
No. I don't think you did.
我认为
I think.
是你叫埃弗拉姆和约拿把我带来这里
that you told Efram and Jonah to bring me here.
折磨我
and to hurt me,
好让你能
and so you arranged to… to…
闯进来救我
…to burst in and save me.
你希望我会感激你
You were hoping that I would be so grateful.
对你言听计从
that I would do anything you said,
对你知无不言
that I would tell you anything that you wanted to know.
为什么 汉娜
Why, Hannah?
我们不是朋友吗
We were friends.
那是你放走梅塔特隆之前
That was before you freed Metatron…
那是
Before…
其他天使 他们恨你
The other angels, they hate you.
那你呢 你也恨我吗
And what about you? Do you hate me?
无所谓了
It doesn't matter.
我们投了票 民主决议
We took a vote… democracy in action…
汉娜必须服从
and… Hannah's doing the job.
我不会把萨姆和迪恩供出来的
I won't give you Sam and Dean.
你当然会
Sure you will.
我们要入侵你的大脑
We're gonna hack your brain.
不管那房子里的是什么
Whatever's in that house,
我能嗅到它辐射出来的法力
I can taste the power radiating from it.
珍娜
Oh, Jenna!
你吓死我了
You scared me.
那东西
That thing…
它很古老
It's old…
你在楼上掉了一颗保龄球吗
What'd you do, drop a bowling ball up there?
很深
…deep…
珍娜
Jenna?
很黑暗
…dark.
亲爱的 你没事吧
Honey, are you all right?
我一直想试试这个
I always wanted to try this.
珍娜
Jenna?
Jenna!
哎呦 出现转折了
Well, hello, plot twist.
有发现吗
Anything?
还没有
Not yet.
你说你知道怎么干的
You said you knew how to do this.
我看娜奥米做过一次
I watched Naomi… once.
够了
Enough!
听着 你不想脏了自己的手 没关系
Look, you don't want to get your pretty hands dirty, fine.
那就走吧 但这事势在必行 给我
Walk away. But this is happening. Gimme.
别动
Now hold still.
这下要疼了
This one might hurt.
我叫你住手
I said stop.
你再敢拦我
You get in my way again…
你再敢碰我 看我
You touch me again, and I…
灭了
…will…
你
…end you!
埃弗拉姆
Uh, Efram.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
不
No!
No.
不
萨姆 萨姆
Sam, Sam.
Sam. Sam.
你没事
You're fine.
你没事 你没事 你没事
You're fine, you're fine, you're fine, you're fine.
你不洁 《圣经》意义上的不洁
You're unclean in the biblical sense.
（圣经净化）
（净化）
（圣经净化 马克福音9：49）
（必须用火来净化 如同献祭）
（圣油）
不要
Don't!
别这么对你自己 别这么对你自己
Don't do this to yourself. Don't do this to yourself.
我会死的
I'll die.
住手
Stop.
不可以
I can't.
别这么对你自己
Don't do this to yourself.
求你了 住手
Please, stop.
珍
Jen!
珍娜
Jenna!
你不是吧
Really?
怎么了
What?
我们完全不晓得所面对的
We have no idea what.
到底是哪路惊天地泣鬼神的邪恶始祖
ancient, world-shattering evil we're dealing with,
不过你请吧
but go right ahead.
大喊大叫让他知道我们要来了吧
Let him know we're coming!
听好 维尔玛（动画《史酷比》中的女孩） 咱们又不是史酷比帮
Listen, Velma, this isn't the Scooby Gang, okay?
你要么闭嘴要么滚
So either shut up or get out.
别动气 小老虎 我就是想帮忙
Easy, tiger. Just trying to help.
人家更像达芙妮（动画《史酷比》中的女孩）哎
I'm way more of a Daphne.
我们是联系在一起的 迪恩
We're bound, Dean.
我们会永远联系在一起
We'll always be bound.
我们永远都会帮助彼此
We will always help each other.
这孩子喜欢你
The child likes you.
一点都不意外呢
No surprise, really.
你充满了母性光辉
You're very maternal.
我们得找到珍娜
We got to find Jenna.
（纳克尔斯郡医疗中心）
什么
What…
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们去救其他人吧
Let's go save the rest of them.
狗血啊
Drama.
珍娜
Jenna?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
这都是我奶奶的收藏
My grandma collected these things,
但是我一直觉得这些东西都挺…
But I always thought they were so…blah.
别担心 她不介意的
Don't worry. She won't care.
我把她的喉咙割破了
I cut her throat.
你为什么要那么做
Why did you do that?
因为这个女人没有灵魂
Because this woman doesn't have a soul.
有意思
Fascinating.
你在说什么 这怎么可能
What are you talking about? How is that even possible?
阿玛拉饿了
Amara's hungry.
她正在长身体
She's a growing girl.
珍娜 听我说
Jenna. Listen to me.
无论发生了什么 无论怎么回事
Whatever's happened, whatever's going on,
我们都能解决好的
we can fix it, okay?
可我不想解决
But I don't want to be fixed.
我喜欢这个崭新的我
I like the new me.
她挺有个性的
She's a ball.
跟我们走 好不好
Just come with us, okay?
珍娜 住手
Jenna! Stop!
我无聊了
I was getting bored.
你杀了她
You killed her!
不客气咯
You're welcome.
你去哪
Where are you going?
去看那个吃灵魂的孩子
To see the child that eats souls.
你不明白那是什么东西
You don't get what that thing is.
洗耳恭听
Enlighten me.
亲爱的 别欲擒故纵嘛
Come on, darling. Don't play coy.
阿玛拉应该就是黑暗
I think Amara is the Darkness.
有意思
Interesting.
那现在怎么办
So, what now?
你去杀了她吗 你吗
You kill her? You?
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
拜托
Please.
就算你可以杀婴儿
Even if you could murder a baby,
你也杀不了那个婴儿
you couldn't murder that baby.
我看见你看她的样子了
I saw the way you looked at her.
而我呢
Me, on the other hand,
这又不是我第一次了
it's not like it'd be my first.
你是主动提供帮助吗
Oh, is that an offer?
是个承诺 等我解决了她的
It's a promise … right after I'm done with her.
别碰她
Stay away from her!
迪恩
Oh, Dean.
可爱的小迪恩啊
Adorable little Dean.
我想要那个孩子 而我总能如愿以偿
I want that child, and I get what I want.
你和萨姆不明白
You and Sam don't understand.
我不是你们的小跟班
I'm not your bloody sidekick!
我们共度过一些美好时光
We've had some good times.
所以我要给你一次机会…
So I'm gonna give you one chance …
就一次…走出那扇门
Just one … to walk out that door,
不然我就把你一点点分解了
Or I'm gonna take you apart atom by atom.
你明白吗
Do you understa…
混蛋
Bastard!
好吧 我还是不明白
All right, I still don't understand.
我以为黑暗是个女人
I mean, I thought the darkness was a woman,
而不是孩子
not a child.
我也这么以为的
Well, same here.
我不知道 也许我之前看到的不是真的
I don't know. Maybe whatever I saw wasn't real.
也许只是个幻象
Maybe it was a vision.
幻象
Vision?
是啊
Yeah.
挺奇怪的
Pretty weird.
是啊 奇怪里面最最奇怪的
Yeah, weird with a weird cherry on a weird top.
我们得找个女佣
We got to get a maid.
就那种 穿着紧身制服的
But, you know, one with a-a little uniform.
有大…
and really big, uh …
救救我
Help me.
天呐 瞧瞧你长成了这么个小可爱
My, haven't you grown into a sweet young thing?
想吃糖吗 小姑娘
Want some candy, little girl?